jpornaccess.com 2017-12-15

# JPornAccess.com | Privacy Policy

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

## Data collection at JPornAccess.com

When you register your membership at our website, you are required to provide your personal information including but not limited to your: user name, password, e-mail address, user information, name, address, telephone number, and credit card information (credit card number  and expiration date). When users request a page display from our server, our server automatically collects user related information including the user’s IP address. Information of your usage status at our website will be also collected through cookies. When E-mails or letters are received from users, we may store such information into our file. We maintain and keep records of all communications between you and our website.

## Disclosure of Personal Data

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or to protect a person's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. We may also share your personal information with: (1) third parties assisting our business operations under contract, including but not limited to fraud investigations and debt collection: (2) law enforcement or other governmental officials if required by law; and (3) with other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity.

## The Way We Use Information:

Your user information will be used for the following reasons: (1) credit card transactions; (2) access or inspection of website; and (3) communication enhancement. Your information may also be used to collect statistics regarding website use; however, the statistics will not contain any information that identify your personally.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us at 213-542-7704 or go to <https://www.allbrightinformation.com/en/index.html>

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.   
If you are under Eighteen Years Old (18), you cannot use our services; therefore, we do not collect any information from individuals who are under Eighteen Years Old (18).

JPornAccess.com is not responsible for any content or privacy policy of the linked websites or websites that place advertisement on our website.
